Finding aid for James D. Standish papers, 1881-1920
Detroit Public Library. Burton Historical Collection.
James D. Standish papers
1881-1920
02940
Detroit Public Library. Burton Historical Collection.
8.1 Linear feet (6 boxes, 17 volumes)
Standish, James D., 1849-1917
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research use.
Biographical/Historical note
Detroit meat packer.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
02940
General Note
See finding aid for complete listing.
Big Horn County Irrigation Co..; Banks and banking; Business records; Correspondence; Detroit (Mich.)--Commerce; Packing-houses--Michigan--Detroit
- BOX 1
  - Abstracts of Title to Standish Subdivision
  - 1905-11 Real Estate
  - 1912-13 Real Estate
  - 1914-17 Real Estate
- BOX 2
  - 1889-1906 Meat Companies
  - 1907-09 Meat Companies
  - 1910-11 Meat Companies
  - 1904-15 Live Stock
- BOX 3
  - 1908-12 Miscellaneous Business
  - 1913-11 Miscellaneous Business
  - 1915-17 Miscellaneous Business
  - 1915-16 Stocks and Securities
- BOX 4
  - 1906-1916 Banking
  - 1908-1914 Personal Correspondence
  - 1915-1916 Personal Correspondence
- BOX 5
  - 1905-1907 Big Horn County Irrigating Co.
  - 1908 Big Horn County Irrigating Co.
  - 1909 Big Horn County Irrigation Co.
  - 1910-1911 Big Horn County Irritating Co.
  - 1912-1915 Big Horn County Irrigating Co.
- BOX 6
  - 1910-1912 South Omaha and Stockyards National Bank
  - 1913-1916 Stockyards National Bank
  - 1907-1916 Cattle Feeders Loan Co.
  - LETTER BOOKS
    - Alcona Stock Farms 1902-1906
    - -- 1903-1906
    - -- 1906-1914
    - Bondholders Committee 1902-1939
    - Bi Horn County Irrigating Co. Trustee 1898-1916
    - A8 -- 1917
    - C4 -- 1912-1915
    - I6 -- 1912
    - I6 -- 1914
    - C2 -- 1896-1899
    - D5 -- 1902-1904
    - L4 -- 1902
    - Personal Calling Cards